Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Senate, Records SC0193
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Memorial resolutions, Accession ARCH_1985_015
  - Gilbert, C. H. (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Girshick, Meyer Abraham (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Golder, Frank Alfred (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Goodier, James Norman (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Gould, Robert Gordon, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Graham, Joseph John (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Grant, Joseph Donohoe (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Gray, Henry David (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Green, Rufus Lot (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Gregory, Thomas Tingey (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Griffin, James Owen (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Guerard, Albert Leon (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Hall, Harvey Monroe (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Hall, Howard Judson (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Hansen, Hazel D. (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Hansen, William Webster (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Hanzlik, Paul John (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Harcourt, Robert Henry (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Hare, Milton Dixon (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Harriman, Raymond Davis (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Harris, Christine Phelps (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Harris, David (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Harsh, Philip Whaley (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Hatcher, Cly Howard (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Heath, Harold (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Hedberg, John (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Heffner, Hubert (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Hempl, George (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Herrmann, Alicia Golebiewska (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Hetenyi, Miklos (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Hewlett, Albion Walter (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Hoisholt, Andrew William (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Holden, Paul E. (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Holman, Emile Frederic (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Holsti, Rudolf (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Horsley, Imogene (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Hoskins, Leander Miller (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Hoover, Theodore Jesse (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Houck, George H. (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Hudson, Hoyt Hopewell (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Hulme, Edward Maslin (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Hunt, Ernest Paul (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Huston, Charles Andrew (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Hutton, Colin Osborne (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Ichihashi, Yamato (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Irvine, William (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Jackson, J. Hugh (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Jacobsen, Lydik Siegumfeldt (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Jahns, Richard H. (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - James, Maud Merrill (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Jenkins, Oliver Peebles (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Johnson, Francis Rarick (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Johnston, Oliver Martin (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Jones, Eliot (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Jones, Richard Foster (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Kaplan, Henry Seymour (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Keesing, Felix Maxwell (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Kefauver, Grayson Neikirk (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Kennedy, Arthur Garfield (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Kindy, Ward Beecher (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Kinney, Lucien Blair (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Kirkwood, Marion Rice (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Kliachko, Sarra (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Knapp, Maud Lombard (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Koenig, Frederick Otto (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Kompfner, Rudolf (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Kreps, Theodore J. (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Langnecker, Harry Leslie (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Lanz, Henry (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Lapp, John Clarke (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Lawrence, Bessie (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Leavelle, Arnaud Bruce (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Leib, Samuel Franklin (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Lemaitre, Georges Edouard (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Lenox, Lionel Remond (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Lesley, Everett Parker (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Lewis, John Kent (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Lilfencrantz, Eric (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Linvill, William K. (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Loewner, Charles (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Long, Royce Reed (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Loring, Hubert Scott (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Luckett, George Sparr (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Lutz, Ralph Haswell (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - McBain, James William (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - McClelland, John Mill (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - McCracken, Mary Isabel (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - McDaniel, Henry Bonner (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - McDowell, John Ezra (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - McKinsey, J. C. C. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - MacFarland, Frank Mace (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - McMurphy, James Ira Wilson (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Manning, William Albert (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Manwaring, Wilfred Hamilton (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mark, Charles David (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Martin, Ernest Whitney (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Martin, Lillien Jane (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Martin, Percy Alvin (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Marx, Guido Hugo (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mazour, Anatole Gregory (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mehrtens, Henry George (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mendelowitz, Daniel M. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Meritt, Herbert Dean (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Meyer, Arthur William (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Miller, Alexander (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mirrielees, Edith Ronald (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mitchell, John Pearce (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Moreno, Halcott Cadwalader (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Morgan, Bayard Quincy (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Morgan, Percy T. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Morrison, Stanley (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Moser, Charles (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Muller, Siemon William (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Murray, Augustus Taber (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Naughton, Alexander E. A. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Newell, Robert Reid (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Newman, Henry Wise (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Nielsen, Oswald (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Niles, Alfred Salem (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Noller, Carl Robert (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Northway, William Herrick (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Odell, William R. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Ogg, Richard Andrew, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Ophuls, William (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Owens, William Brownlee (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Osborne, George Edward (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Packer, Herbert L. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Page, Robert Meredith (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Parlee, Norman Allen Devine (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Parks, George Sutton (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Pashin, Nicholas S. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Pederson, Carlton A. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Peffer, E. Louise (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Peirce, George James (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Pettit, Albert Victor (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Pool, Judith Braham (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Potter, David M. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Price, George Clinton (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Proctor, William M. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Quillen, I. James (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Rantz, Lowell Addison (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Reichert, Frederick Leet (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Reid, Elliott Gray (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Reinhardt, Kurt Frank (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Reining, Charles (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Rendtorff, Karl Gustav (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Reynolds, Charles Nathan (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Reynolds, Leon Benedict (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Rich, Willis Horton (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Ripley, Julien A. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Rixford, Emmet (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Robichek, Alexander A. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Rogat, Yosal (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Rogers, Austin Flint (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Rogers, Frederick John (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Roggeveen, Vincent (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Rosaldo, Michelle Zimbalist (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Ross, Perley Ason (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Running, Carl Trygve (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Ryan, Harris Joseph (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Ryfkogel, Henry Anthon Lewis (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Sanford, Fernando (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Sapirstein, Leo Abraham (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Schenck, Hubert Gregory (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Schiff, Leonard I. (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Schultz, Edwin William (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Sears, Jesse Brundage (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Seifert, Howard Stanley (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Seward, Samuel Swayze (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Shafer, George Daniel (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Shepherd, Harold (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Shirley, Hale Foreman (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Silberling, Norman John (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Simpson, Claude M. (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Skogsberg, Karl Jonas Tage (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Sloan, William Henry (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Slonaker, James Rollin (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Sloss, Leon (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Show, Arley Barthlow (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Smith, Everett Wallace (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Smith, Gilbert Morgan (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Smith, James Perrin (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Smith, Jeffery (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Smith, Stanley Astredo (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Snyder, John Otterbein (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Sokol, Anthony E. (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Somers, George B. (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Sonkin, Simon (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Soske, Joshua Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Spalding, Alfred Baker (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Spurr, William A. (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Stanford, Thomas Welton (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Stanley, Edward John (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Starks, Edwin Chapin (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Stauf, Ida (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Stebbins, Horatio Ward (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Stillman, John Maxson (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Stillman, Stanley (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Stolz, Lois Meek (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Stoltenberg, Clara s. (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Stone, Calvin Perry (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Storey, Thomas Andrew (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Stow, Vanderlynn (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Strong, Edward Kellogg, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Strothmann, Friedrich W. (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Swain, Robert Eckles (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Sworakowski, Witold S. (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Taylor, Alonzo Englebert (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Taylor, Charles Vincent (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Terman, Frederick Emmons (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Terman, Lewis Madison (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Thompson, Walter (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Tickell, Frederick G. (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Timoshenko, Stephen P. (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Timoshenko, Vladimir P. (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Todd, Lois Pendleton (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Tolman, Cyrus Fisher (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Torrey, Harry Beal (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Townley, Sidney Dean (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Treat, Payson Johnson (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Tresidder, Donald Bertrand (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Twitty, Victor Chandler (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - van Patten, Nathan (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Vennard, John K. (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Vernier, Chester Garfield (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Wallin, Paul (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Watkins, James T. IV (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Watson, William (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Webster, David Locke (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Webster, T.B.L. (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Weir, Ruth, Hirsch (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Weigle, Clifford F. (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Weisz, Alfred E. (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Wells, James Bertrand (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - West, Victor J. (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Weymouth, Frank Walter (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Whitaker, Albert Conser (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Whitaker, Virgil Keeble (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - White, Andrew Dickson (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Whittier, Clarke Butler (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Wickizer, Vernon Dale (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Wilcox, John Marsh (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Wildman, Murray Shipley (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Williams, Harry Andrew (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Williams, Marian (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Willis, Bailey (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Wing, Charles Benjamin (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Winters, Arthur Yvor (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Wyatt, Michael (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Wyckoff, Harry (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Yeager, Anne Stone (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Yost, Mary (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Young, Donovan Harold (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Young, Stewart Woodford (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Miscellaneous (Not Academic Council members) (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Faculty Senate records, 1966-1986; Accession ARCH_1986_127
  - Administrative Forum, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Athletics/D.A.P.E.R Meetings, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cataloging Advisory Council, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Collection Development Council, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Director's Conference, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Club Minutes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty/Staff Housing, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Study Program, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Studies, 1974-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Land and Building Development Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Land and Building Development Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Land and Building Development Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Land and Building Development Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Libraries, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Libraries, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Library Acquisition Council, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Library Administrative Conference, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Library Cabinet Minutes, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Library Council Minutes, 1970-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Library Curator's Group, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Public Service's Council, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Public Service's Council, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Outdoor Art, Sub-Committee on, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Research, Committee on, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee on Closing the Card Catalog, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Technical Service's Group Minutes, 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Studies (C-US) Minutes, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Studies (C-US) Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Studies (C-US) Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Studies (C-US) Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Committees (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Academic Council records, 1891-1989; Accession ARCH_1989_214
  - Faculty minutes, 10/31/1891 to 2/19/1904 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 5/4/1904 - 5/25/1910 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 9/9/1910 - 1/4/1916 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 9/10/1915 - 6/14/1918 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/4/1918 - 10/6/1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1/5/1923 - 6/10/1924 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/9/1924 - 4/1/1927 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 6/17/1927 - 6/17/1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/4/1929 - 6/7/1932 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/7/1932 - 6/15/1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/15/1934 - 1/8/1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 4/2/1937 - 6/19/1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 9/30/1938 - 6/15/1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 9/26/1941 - 6/11/1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/15/1943 - 6/11/1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/1/1948 - 6/16/1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 9/29/1950 - 1/19/1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 4/3/1953 - 6/7/1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 9/30/1955 - 5/5/1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 6/14/1957 - 6/14/1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/2/1959 - 9/29/1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 11/27/1961 - 6/12/1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/2/1964 - 10/25/1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1/6/1967 - 6/16/1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/4/1968 - 1/8/1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 4/2/1971 - 4/11/1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 10/3/1975 - 4/4/1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council, 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council, 1963-1065 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Academic Council Winter and Spring, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Academic Council, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council ROTC Referendum (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council Review re: Foreign Language (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Review re: Research (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council ROTC Review (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Academic Council Referendum on ROTC (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Academic Council Referendum re: Laos, 3/71 - 4/71 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Academic Council Review-Faculty Self Discipline (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Academic Council Winter, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Academic Council File ACD #0001- (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Academic Council Referendum, 30683 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Academic Council Autumn, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Academic Council Spring, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council Elections, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Special Election, 24593 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Senate Elections, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Senate Elections, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Senate Elections, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Senate Elections, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Senate Elections, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Senate Elections, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Senate Elections, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Senate Elections, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Senate Elections, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Senate Elections, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Senate Elections, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Senate Elections, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Senate Elections, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Advisory Board Elections, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Senate Elections, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Senate and Advisory Board Elections, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Computer Results, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Computer Results, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Computer Results, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Computer Results, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Computer Results, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Computer Results, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Computer Results Reference Guide (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 10/11/1904-06/05/1907 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 10/03/1907-05/13/1910 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 10/21/1910-11/18/1915 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, Index of, 9/16/1909-4/18/1916 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 09/16/1915-03/03/1926 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 05/12/1926-06/05/1945 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 10/30/1945-06/01/1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 10/03/1956-07/17/1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 09/26/1962-06/06/1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 06/14/1967-06/14/1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate V-XII, 1973-1979 (Box 10)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XII-XIII, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XIII-XIV, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XV-XVI, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XVI-XVII, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XVIII-XIX, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XIX-XX, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 Jan 8; 16_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 1)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 Jan 8; 16_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 2)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 1), 1987 Jan 15; 16_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 3)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 Jan 22; 16_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 4)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 Jan 22; 16_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 5)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 Feb 5; 16_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 6)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 Feb 5; 16_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 7)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 Feb 19; 16_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 8)